欢迎加入OCR小组 qq群906722936 字幕优先发布于群内
威灵顿督查 你觉得他最近
Inspector Wellington- - how have you
-状态怎么样  -我有点担心他
found him recently? I'm concerned about him.
你需要休息
You need to rest.
睡觉现在对我来说太过奢侈
Sleep is a luxury that I don't have at the moment.
明晚有时间一起吃晚饭吗
Are you free to dine tomorrow evening?
那就明晚见吧
Tomorrow evening it is, then.
警察 放下武器
WILLIAM: Policel Put down your weapons!
我说放下武器 马上
I said put them down, now!
威灵顿督察他
It's Inspector Wellington.
他中弹了
He's been shot.
医生也不确定他能不能挺过来
They cannot say for certain if he will survive.
抱歉我今天迟到了
Sorry I'm late today.
有一个新来的病房护士
There's a new ward sister,
她一开始不让我进来
and she wouldn't let me in at first.
我把我母亲的戒指戴在了无名指上
I put my mother's ring on my wedding finger
跟她说你是我丈夫
and told her you were my husband.
她得知你名草有主了
She seemed a little disappointed
好像还有点小失望
that you were, perhaps, taken.
我觉得你在护士中间引起了不少的关注 威廉
I think you've made quite a stir amongst the nurses, William.
大家对于我天天来看你意见不太一致
Everyone has a different opinion of my visits with you.
艾薇认为我应该坐在这跟你聊天
Ivy believes I should just sit and talk to you
就像什么都没发生一样
as if nothing's happened.
菲茨罗伊警探建议我大声
Detective Fitzroy suggested reading aloud
读俄国小说
from a Russian novel,
不过那本小说的名字我读不出来
the title of which I cannot pronounce.
我猜这样可能会激怒你 然后你坐起身来
I suppose it might provoke you into sitting up
求我别再读了
and begging me to stop.
而波茨先生
And Mr. Potts
波茨先生出乎意料的体贴周到
Well, Mr. Potts was surprisingly thoughtful.
他建议说 既然你最讨厌别人喋喋不休
He advised that as you are a man who despises a lot of chatter,
那我在这坐着陪你就行
that I should merely sit with you.
这应该就足够了
That would be company enough.
拜托你醒过来吧
Please wake up.
威廉
: William.
醒醒
Wake up.
Wake up!
醒醒
WOMAN: Wake up!
我说 醒醒
I said, "Wake up! "
12年前
离开这里 快
: Get out of here! Shoo!
给我出来 赶紧 滚蛋
Get out of herel Go on, bugger off!
滚蛋
Bugger off.
-快滚  -好了好了 我这就走了
Bugger off! All right, all right, I'm going!
你要点什么
What can I get you, huh?
我只是想问问你这货摊
I was just wondering if you needed
要不要请人帮忙
some help running the stall.
不用
No.
我工作可卖力了
I'm a hard worker.
我今天可以免费给你干一天
I'|I work for free for today so you can see
-让你看看我干的多好  -我说不用了
how good I am. I said no.
拜托了
Please.
我两天没吃东西了
I haven't eaten in two days.
要什么 亲
Yes, darling?
请给我来条面包
WOMAN: Loaf of bread, please.
当然
Yes, of course.
嘿 嘿
STALL KEEPER: Hey! Hey!
嘿
Heyl
天啊
: Dear God.
早
MAN: Morning
早 早
WOMAN: Morning. Morning.
怎么回事
What on Earth?
丽兹
Lizzie!
你怎么回家来了
What are you doing home?
你被开除了
You've been expelled!
没有 不算是
No! Well, not exactly.
我被要求立刻离开那里
I was told to leave the premises with immediate effect.
这难道还不是被开除吗
How is that not being expelled?
那又不是所学校 艾薇
It's not a school, Ivy.
只是个培训学院
It's a training college.
从学院出来不叫开除 叫勒令退学
You're not expelled from a college, you get sent down.
哦 请原谅我的无知
Oh, pardon my ignorance.
我都记不得你从多少个地方
I've lost track of how many places
被人给勒令退学了
you've been sent down from.
又不是我的错
It's not my fault.
我不想做
I don't want to be
家庭教师或者学校老师
a governess or a schoolmistress,
或任何这种类型的工作
or any of those things.
而且我本就计划要回来的
And I was planning to come back anyway.
我收到了父亲有关斯奇普的信
I got Father's letter about Skip.
哦 所以你父亲的狗死了
Oh, so your father's dog dies,
而正好你也被
and that just happens to coincide
-勒令退学了  -那不是他的狗
with you being expelled. It's not his dog,
那是我们家的狗 是我非常爱的狗
it's the family dog, whom I very much loved.
这不是问题的关键 而且你也知道
That is not the point, and you know it!
你都16岁了 丽兹
You're 16 years old, Lizzie!
你也该长大了
It's time you grew up!
如果我想听人吼我 那我不如
Well, if I wanted to get shouted at, I would"ve stayed
留在学院了
at college.
而且我真的很爱那条狗
And I really did love that dog.
我们要拿你怎么办呢
What are we going to do with you?
天知道你父亲会说什么
God only knows what your father's going to say.
摄影师在路上了吗
: Is the photographer on his way?
是的 斯嘉丽督查
Yes, Inspector Scarlet.
我认识这个人
I know this man.
我们以前一起工作过
We used to work together.
他叫
His name's, um...
沃利斯
Wallis.
亚瑟·沃利斯
Arthur Wallis.
看上去不太像是抢劫
Doesn't seem like a robbery, though.
是谁发现的他
Who was it that found him?
下午好
Good afternoon.
我都在这待几小时了 到底怎么回事啊
I've been here hours- - what's going on?
你需要向总调查官
You were asked to give a statement
做份口供
to the chief investigating officer?
就是我
That would be me.
我是亨利·斯嘉丽总督察 你是
My name's Detective Inspector Henry Scarlet- - and you are?
我已经给过口供了啊
I've already given a statement.
我就是路过
I was walking past,
看到了一具尸体 我走开去找人帮忙 现在我能走了吗
I saw a body, I went and got help can I go now?
你的姓名
Yeah, your name, please?
威廉·威灵顿
William Wellington.
威灵顿
Wellington.
跟那个公爵同姓吗
As in the duke?
谁
Who?
现在学校都教啥啊
What are they teaching you in schools these days?
你最好别想着
You'd better not be thinking
把这脏水泼到我身上
of fitting me up for this.
我可听说过你们伦敦警察
I've heard about London bobbies.
没人指控你任何事
No one is accusing you of anything.
毕竟很少有杀人犯把警察叫到
I mean, very few murderers would bring the police
-犯罪现场  -我再不去工作就丢了
to a crime scene. I'm missing work.
我在一个馅饼摊上班
I've a job on a pie stall.
如果我不及时赶到就没的干了
I'l| lose it if I don't get back there.
要么你在这回答我的问题
You either answer my questions here
要么就跟我去苏格兰场
or down at Scotland Yard.
-你自己选  -给我让开
Your choice. : Get out of my way!
你不能把我丢在这
WILLIAM: You can't leave me in here!
我要去趟停尸房
I'm going to the city mortuary.
等我回来时 带他来我办公室
When I get back, bring him to my office.
是 长官
OFFICER: Yes, sir.
丽兹 有人来看你
Lizzie? There's someone here to see you.
谁啊
Well, who is it?
帕克太太和她儿子
Mrs. Parker and her son.
不不不 告诉他们我 我
No, no, no, tell them I'm, I'm...MRS. PARKER: Ah!
你说的对啊 鲁伯特
You were correct, Rupert.
斯嘉丽小姐还真回来了
Miss Scarlet has returned.
那你们聊吧
I'll leave you to it.
非常感谢 艾薇
Thank you so much, Ivy.
帕克太太
Mrs. Parker.
帕克先生 什么风
Mr. Parker- to what do I owe
把你们给吹来了
this unexpected pleasure?
鲁伯特今早在摄政公园散步
Rupert was taking his morning stroll in Regent's Park,
碰巧遇到了你的邻居 威廉姆斯医生
when he came across your neighbor Dr. Williams.
好心的医生提了一嘴
The good doctor mentioned
说看到你回家来了
that he had seen you returning home,
还带着手提箱
suitcase in hand.
鲁伯特跟我说了
Rupert relayed this to me,
我就说 这不可能啊
and I said, "Oh, this cannot be correct.
斯嘉丽小姐在温布尔顿接受家庭教师的培训呢
Miss Scarlet is in Wimbledon, training to be a governess. "
学期结束了 我是回来休假的
Term has finished, and I have returned home for the holidays.
这学期要再过三周才结束
The academic term does not end for another three weeks.
没发生什么不好的事吧
I trust nothing untoward has occurred?
我同学和我学习任务完成的好
Well, my classmates and I were making such good progress,
所以我们就被允许
we were permitted
提前结业了
to finish early.
我可要提醒你 斯嘉丽小姐
I would remind you, Miss Scarlet,
你父亲和你是我的房客
that yourself and your father are my tenants,
你名誉受损
and a stain on your reputation
那我的名誉也会沾污
is a stain on mine.
帕克太太 你的名誉在我心里
Mrs. Parker, your reputation is always at the forefront
一直都是最重要的
of my mind.
真高兴听到你这么说
I'm glad to hear it.
那现在我们就吃点茶点吧
And now we shall take refreshments.
我来杯茶
I shall take tea.
鲁伯特就不喝了
Rupert will not.
你的口供说不通啊
HENRY: Your statement makes little sense.
好吧 我们再来一遍
AlI right, let's try this one again.
你说你经过
So, you say you were walking past
看到了尸体后就去寻求帮助
when you saw the body and you went to get help.
那你当时是要走去哪呢
Well, where were you walking to, exactly,
那里可是个死胡同啊
given that it's a dead end?
我是这么想的 你应该是睡在胡同里
See, my guess is that you were sleeping in the alleyway.
那些东西不是我的
Those aren't my things.
格拉斯哥的济贫院的离开证明
Document of discharge from a workhouse in Glasgow.
名字是威廉·詹姆斯·威灵顿
In the name William James Wellington.
就是你
That's you.
你露宿街头有多久了
How long have you been living out on the streets?
看你的样子应该有一阵子了
It's a while, by the look of you.
你一定很饿吧
I imagine you're hungry.
我知道你想干什么
I know what you're trying to do.
假装关心我好让我开口
Be nice to me so I'll talk.
我正是这么打算的
That's exactly what I'm trying to do.
所以你到底饿不饿呢
So, are you hungry or not?
你现在去楼下在厨房里等着
Now, if you go downstairs and wait in the kitchen,
我让管家给你准备晚餐
I'll have my housekeeper make you some supper.
去吧
Go on.
丽兹
Lizzie.
你怎么回来了
What are you doing here?
父亲请你先冷静
ELIZA: Father, please calm down.
别告诉我冷静
HENRY: Do not tell me to calm down.
天 你就非要挑战我的耐心吗
God, you would try the patience of a saint!
当初去那个地方也不是我想的
ELIZA: Well, I did not ask to be sent to that place.
你都不知道那里是什么样
You have no idea what it's like.
你不再是个孩子了 丽兹
HENRY: You are not a child anymore, Lizzie.
你得开始表现的像个受人尊重的年轻女性了
You must start behaving like a respectable young woman!
大多数你这个年纪的姑娘都已经嫁人了
And most girls your age would have been married off by now.
这是我们妥协后的解决方案
This was the solution to our compromise.
是你妥协的方案不是我的
Your compromise, not mine.
你知道我想走哪条路
You know what path I wish to follow.
我不想再跟你说了
I cannot have this conversation again.
丽兹 让我们谈谈好吗
Lizzie, give us a moment to talk, hmm?
楼下有个客人
We have a guest downstairs.
你去给他做点东西吃吧
Go and make him something to eat.
我马上下去
I'll be down shortly.
给他做点东西吃吗
: Make him something to eat?
你不是上过烹饪课吗 对吧
You have been attending cookery classes, have you not?
有时候上 对
Um, sometimes, yes.
烤箱上面有一块熏火腿
There's a smoked ham on top of the oven.
给他切一片吧
Give him a slice of that.
晚上好 我是斯嘉丽小姐
Good evening, my name is Miss Scarlet.
我想你应该是
I believe you are.
我父亲的同事吧
...an associate of my father's.
他说这里有吃的
He said there'd be food.
对 我下午熏了块火腿
Yes, I cooked a smoked ham this afternoon.
我给你切一片
I'll cut you a slice.
你怎么认识我父亲的
So, how do you know my father?
你也在警局工作吗
Do you work for the police?
你有面包吗
You got any bread?
我不确定
I'm not sure.
我去看看我今天还做了什么
I shall take a look at what else I made today.
你切的这火腿厚的连子弹都穿不透
You could stop a bullet with that.
你是苏格兰人吗
Uh, you are Scottish?
你从哪来的
Whereabouts are you from?
你平时问题也这么多吗
Do you always ask this many questions?
我去看看有没有面包
I'll see if we have bread.
我听见楼上的争吵声了
I heard shouting just now.
他吼你来着对吧 你爸
He was yelling at you, wasn't he, your pa?
你做错什么了
What did you do?
为什么你觉得是我的错
Why do you assume it was my fault?
我猜对了是吧
I'm right, aren't I?
你做什么了啊
What did you do?
你平时问题也这么多吗
Do you always ask this many questions?
我想喝点水
I'll have some water.
水槽在那边
Sink's just there.
我是客人来着
I'm a guest in this house.
那你就该表现出客人该有的礼貌
Well, then, perhaps you might show some basic courtesy.
就从说“请”和“谢谢”开始吧
We'll start with"pleaseand"thank you, "
然后再规范一下你的吃相 要像个绅士而不是头
then move on to eating like a gentleman and not a pig.
狼吞虎咽的猪
In a trough.
她变成这样都是我的错
It's my fault she lost her way.
她母亲过世后是我把她惯坏了
I indulged her after her mother died.
这孩子从打出生时起就很固执
That girl was born headstrong.
无论你怎么做都改变不了她
Nothing you could've done would've changed that.
是我鼓励了她对我工作的兴趣
I encouraged her to be interested in my work.
帮了倒忙
Did her a disservice.
给了她永远无法实现的野心
Gave her ambitions she can never fulfill.
但是
But...
现在我得去跟我们的客人聊两句了
Right now, I must speak to our guest.
感觉今晚不好过啊
I fear I have a long night ahead of me.
你给他东西吃了吗
IVY: Did you give him something to eat?
给了 但他走开了
I tried to, but he walked out.
不是我的错
It wasn't my fault.
这么糟糕吗
IVY: That bad, is it?
什么
What?
你只有在感到内疚时才做家务
You only do chores when you're feeling guilty.
父亲在哪
Where's Father?
他一整晚都在外面找那个年轻人
He's been out all night looking for that young man.
早上回来换了身衣服吃了点早餐
Came back early for a change of clothes and some breakfast,
就又出去了
then went out again.
你跟他说过话吗
Did you speak to him?
坐下吧 丽兹
Sit down, Lizzie.
现在你爸挺难的
Things are hard for him at the moment.
你母亲留下的钱
The money that your mother left,
已经要用完了
it's running out.
这房子又不便宜
And this house is expensive to keep.
他是个骄傲的人 从不肯承认
He's a proud man, and he'll never admit it,
但这些事给了他很大的压力
but these things weigh heavily on his shoulders.
所以
So,
如果你想帮他
if you want to help him,
就听他的吧
just do as he asks.
那就意味着你可能要做些
And that might mean doing some things
你不想做的事
that you don't want to do.
比如呢
Well, what kind of things?
我们没有在等什么客人吧
Oh, we're not expecting any visitors,
对吗
are we?
之前你母亲过世那会儿
Some time ago, after your mother's passing,
我跟你父亲说
I spoke to your father
想让你来我这
and offered to take you under my wing,
教你一些年轻女士
to give you the kind of education
该学的东西
a young lady ought to be receiving.
他一开始拒绝了
He declined, initially.
但我收到他的口信
But I have received a note from him
说他愿意考虑我的提议
saying he wishes to take me up on my kind offer.
怎么回事
MAN: Excuse me?
抱歉
Sorry.
给我吧 谢谢
HENRY: I'II take that, thank you.
你怎么找到我的
How did you find me?
所有人都觉得自己很特别
Oh, everybody thinks themselves unique,
但其实我们都有可以预估到的行为模式
but we all have patterns of behavior that can be predicted.
比如你吧
Take you, for example.
你是格拉斯哥来的
You're from Glasgow.
所以你的火车应该是到国王十字车站的
So your train would have arrived at King's Cross station.
所以我想你是留在这个区域找工作了
Now, I suspect that you stayed in the area looking for work,
但不成功
but were unsuccessful.
于是你现在露宿街头
Hence why you're now sleeping on the streets.
所以你不得已
So, to rectify the situation, you turned
开始了低级盗窃现在
to low- level theft- - now, there are
国王十字区有五条街上
five streets in the King's Cross area
扒窃盛行
where pickpocketing is rife.
这是我试过的第三条街
This is the third one I tried.
你找我到底想干嘛
What do you want from me?
告诉我你在胡同里看到了什么
Tell me what you saw in the alley.
那对我有什么好处
What's in it for me?
在我看来
Well, from what I can tellj
你是个聪明的年轻人
you're an intelligent young man.
你帮我 我也会想办法帮你
Help me, and I will help you in whatever way I can.
毕竟你也不想大老远跑了400多英里来做个小偷吧
I mean, you didn't travel 400 miles just to be a pickpocket.
你看到谋杀现场了 对吧
You saw the murder take place, didn't you?
好 走吧
Okay, come on.
我们将接待
We shall be hosting the ladies
肯辛顿慈善基金会的女士们
of the Kensington Benevolent Fund.
她们为伦敦的穷人和有需求的人
They have raised thousands of pounds
筹集了数千英镑
for the poor and needy of London, and
不不不
No, no, no!
用韦奇伍德瓷器 动动脑姑娘
The Wedgwood china- - think, girl.
抱歉夫人
Sorry, ma'am.
客人到了之后 你要恭顺有礼貌
When the guests arrive, you will be polite and deferential.
说话的时候
When speaking,
要口齿清晰
do so with clear diction.
远离有争议的话题
Stay away from contentious topics,
谈点自己的兴趣爱好就行
and talk instead of your hobbies and interests.
你有兴趣爱好吧
You do have hobbies and interests?
我喜欢读我父亲的书
Well, I love to read my father's books.
太好了
Marvelous.
尤其喜欢读
In particular, the ones
法医病理学方面的
on forensic pathology.
有一章我读了有20几遍
There's this one chapter I must have read 20 times
讲的是关于尸斑的
about the livor mortis.
血液在静脉和动脉中的死后沉淀
The postmortem settling of the blood in the veins
通常可以表明
and arteries that can often indicate
尸体是否在谋杀后
whether a body has been moved
被移动过
after a murder.
把蛋糕架的
Fetch the doilies
小垫子拿来
for the cake stand.
一个好佣人
A good servant,
ChatGPT中文版
免安装\信扫码知刻使用
这就是未来
就像个好孩子
like a good child,
需要被看到 但不需要被听到
must be seen, but not heard.
不过毫无疑问
But have no doubt
等他们独处时
that when they are alone,
他们会谈论我们在他们面前说过的事
they talk of the things we have said in their presence.
ChatGPT中文版
免安装V信扫码即刻使用
这就是未来
因此我们绝不能说任何
Therefore, it is imperative that we say nothing odd or peculiar
影响到我们主人地位的
that could undermine our position
-古怪或者奇特的话  -但我只是说
as their superiors. But I only said
as their superiors. But I only said...
早晚有一天你会结婚
Someday, you will be married.
你的丈夫必须对你管家的能力
And your husband must feel confident in your ability
充满信心
to run a household.
说到结婚
Speaking of marriage,
鲁伯特对任何年轻女士都没有兴趣
Rupert rarely has an interest in any young ladies,
但他一直在不断打听你
but he is continually asking questions about you.
我想他应该是觉得你很有吸引力吧
I believe he finds you quite fascinating.
帕克太太
Mrs. Parker.
你父亲经济拮据
Your father is a man of limited means.
鲁伯特是我的财产继承人
Rupert is the heir to my fortune.
如果你们俩能在一起我觉得这对
I believe it would be a beneficial arrangement
双方的家庭来说都是好事
for both our families.
现在 坐下吧
Now, take a seat,
让我看看你的仪态如何
and we shall look at your posture.
有时候回到犯罪现场
Sometimes being back at the crime scene
可以帮助唤起我们不知道的记忆
can help trigger memories we didn't know we had.
你说你当时是坐着的
So, you said you were sat down.
我 我当时就睡在这些桶后面
I, I was asleep behind those barrels.
但有动静把你吵醒了
Mm- hmm, but something woke you up.
我听见了脚步声
I heard footsteps.
有人在跑
Someone running.
两个人在跑
Two people running.
其中一个是你的朋友 沃利斯先生
One was your friend, Mr. Wallis.
另一个要年轻一点
The other was younger.
20 21岁左右的样子
Like, 20, 21, something like that.
很好 继续
Good, good, go on.
那个年轻人将沃利斯先生
The younger man threw Mr. Wallis
朝墙上推过去
up against that wall,
然后就开始掐他的脖子
which is when he started to strangle him.
然后又把他丢到了地上
Then he threw him to the ground.
你能描述一下袭击者吗
Well, can you describe the attacker?
金发
Fair hair.
高个子可能有1.82左右
Uh, tall, perhaps six feet.
看上去挺有钱
And rich- looking.
-衣着光鲜  -还有什么
Fancy clothes. What else?
他掐他脖子的时候
WILLIAM: As he was strangling him,
跪了下来 低声说了点什么
he knelt down and whispered something.
就好像
It was as if.
好像他认识他
As if he knew him.
这可真是个美妙的夜晚
It really was the most wonderful evening.
食物由布拉汉姆酒店的厨师长
The food was prepared by Marcel Laurent himself,
马塞尔·劳伦亲自烹制
the chef de cuisine at the Brabham Hotel.
哈珀·琼斯夫人
Lady Harper Jones is the jewel
是我们社交圈的大红人
in the crown of our social circle.
但我觉得自己说的太多了
Oh, but I fear I have been talking too long.
让我们聊聊
Let us learn more
斯嘉丽小姐吧
about our Miss Scarlet.
给我讲讲你自己 亲爱的
Tell me about yourself, my dear.
斯嘉丽小姐兴趣广泛
MRS. PARKER: Miss Scarlet has
其中包括刺绣
a number of interests, including embroidery
和水彩画
and watercolors.
遇到一位有着如此健康兴趣的
HARPER JONES: Well, it is reassuring
年轻女士真是令人安心
to meet a young lady with such wholesome interests.
你今晚一定要到博恩伯勒大厅来参加我们的聚会
You must join us this evening at Bornborough Hall.
我要给我女儿的生日举办一个派对
I'm holding a soiree for my daughter's birthday.
鲁伯特也去
Rupert is going.
我想他一定非常愿意陪你一起去
I'm sure he would be delighted to escort you.
这可太有心了 但是
That is most kind, but it is
真是个绝妙的主意
A splendid idea.
我不得不承认
I confess, Miss Scarlet
鲁伯特对斯嘉丽小姐十分有兴趣
has quite piqued my Rupert's interest.
当然 我还要问一下我父亲
Well, I will, of course, have to ask my father.
你父亲已经把你交给我了
Your father has put his faith in me
相信我会照顾好你的
to look after your best interests.
鲁伯特8点去接你
Rupert will pick you up at 8: 00.
好极了
Marvelous.
不在这些人中
It wasn't any of these.
我可能要扩大下范围了
I may cast the net a little wider,
让你再多看几张照片 但今天不行
get you to look at a few more, but not today.
让你的眼睛先休息一下
Give your eyes a rest.
你做警察多久了
How long have you been a copper?
1848年11月10日加入警局
Signed up on November 10, 1848.
是23年了吗 不对
So that's 23? Ooh, God, no.
24年了
24 years ago.
时间飞逝啊
Tempus fugit.
什么
What?
时间飞逝
Time flies.
我跟受害人亚瑟是同一周加入的
I joined the same week as Arthur, our murder victim.
你们曾是朋友吗
You were friends?
对 有段时间是
Mmm, you know, for a while.
但这个地方可能不适合他吧
I just don't think this place was really for him.
他离开后做了私家侦探
He left to become a private detective.
你昨晚住哪了
Where did you sleep last night?
不知道 好像是一个地方的门口
I don't know, it was some doorway.
我家房子还有空房间
There's a spare room at my house.
你可以在那住几晚
You can have a bed for a few nights.
你为什么要这么做
Why would you do that?
我需要能随时找到你
Well, I need you where I can find you.
但如果你要留下
But if you are gonna stay,
就得先把自己清理干净
you're gonna have to clean yourself up a bit, I mean,
我的管家要是看你这样睡在床单上
my housekeeper's gonna have a fit if you lie on her sheets
肯定会大发雷霆的
like that.
汉诺威广场有个洗衣房
There's a public washhouse on Hanover Square,
你可以在那洗衣服 刮胡子 再泡个澡
so wash your clothes, have a shave, take a bath.
我想你只有这一身衣服吧
Iassume they're your only clothes.
说实话
Well, to tell the truth,
这身衣服也不是我的
they're not even mine. Right, well,
去洗衣房的路上有一家旧货店
there's a thrift shop on the way to the washhouse.
麦肯锡
Uh, McKenzie's.
看看能不能买身衣服
See what you can get for that.
你怎么知道我不会拿上钱
How do you know I won't just take your money
然后跑了呢
and run off with it?
我想我只能信任你吧
I guess I'm just gonna have to trust you.
还需要多久啊
: How much longer is this going to take?
该什么时候完事就什么时候完事
It will take as long as it takes.
你站好了
Now stand still.
我不想去这个愚蠢的派对
I don't want to go to this stupid party.
谁不喜欢派对啊
Everybody likes parties.
他们才不喜欢 就口头上说喜欢而已
No, they don't- - they just say they do.
尤其是不想跟鲁伯特·帕克一起去
I certainly don't want to go with Rupert Parker.
我们一天不结婚 他母亲就没法开心
His mother won't be happy until we're man and wife.
我觉得你很安全
Well, I think you're safe there.
我怀疑他就不是能结婚的类型
I doubt he's the marrying type.
为什么这么说
Well, what makes you say that?
搞定了
Done.
你可别再长了 好姑娘
Now, will you please stop growing, young lady?
哦 丽兹
Oh, Lizzie.
你好美
You look beautiful.
跟你母亲好像
I can see your mother in you,
真的
I really can.
当然了 你母亲喜欢笑
Course, your mother used to smile more.
我去开门吧
I'll get that.
你把这儿收拾一下
You can tidy up in here.
把所有东西都放回缝纫筐里去
Put everything back in the sewing box.
整齐点放哈
Uh, neatly, please.
你是威廉吗
IVY: You're William?
斯嘉丽先生说过你会来
Mr. Scarlet said to expect you.
进来吧
Come on in.
外面很冷 别冻感冒了
It's cold out there- - you'll catch your death.
我把客房收拾好了
I've made up the spare room.
你还有其它东西吗
Do you have any other belongings?
没有了
WILLIAM: No, it's just me.
好吧 如果你还需要什么告诉我就行
IVY: Well, if there's anything else you need, just let me know.
你真好人 我会的
WILLIAM: That's very kind of you- - I will.
你饿吗
IVY: Are you hungry?
想吃点什么吗
Would you like something to eat?
是的 拜托了 谢谢
Yes, please- thank you.
你好 又见面了
Hello, again.
你好
Hello.
下楼去厨房吧
Get yourself downstairs to the kitchen.
他为什么回来了
Why's he come back?
这个年轻人会跟我们一起住几天
The young man is going to be staying with us for a few days.
你别再惹他了
And you're to stay away from him, young lady.
帕克先生来之前你还有点时间
Now, you've a bit of time before Mr. Parker is due,
不如你过去把那间卧室整理一下
so why don't you go and tidy that bedroom?
去吧
Go on.
快点
Now.
威灵顿先生
Mr. Wellington.
叫我威廉
It's William.
威廉
: William.
我觉得有件事可能搞错了
I'm afraid there's been something of a mix- up.
父亲还在警察局 但他让人捎了口信
Father is still at work, but he's sent a message
说我们今晚跟朋友们一起吃饭
to say that we are to dine with friends this evening,
他想让你也一起去
and he would like you to come along.
伍兹小姐刚给我做了晚饭
Miss Woods just made me dinner.
艾薇不知道计划有变
Ivy is unaware of this change of plan.
她一直在客厅里做针线活
She is in the drawing room sewing.
我就没打扰她
I didn't want to disturb her.
你有晚礼服吗
Do you own a dinner suit?
让我看看
Let me see.
没有
No.
我叔叔去年在我们这住过 他跟你身高差不多
My uncle stayed with us last year, he is about your height.
他的晚礼服应该在客房的衣柜里
I believe his dinner suit is in the wardrobe in the spare room.
我可不想穿一个老头子的衣服
I'm not wearing some old man's clothes.
我父亲为你打开了家里的大门
My father has opened his house to you.
拒绝这种好心的邀请
Refusing this kind of invitation
可不太合乎礼节
is not the done thing.
我不在乎合不合礼节
I don't care about the done thing.
行吧
Fine.
你可真是个粗鲁的年轻人
You are a very rude young man.
我会如此告诉我父亲
I will tell my father as much.
-帕克先生  -斯嘉丽小姐
Mr. Parker. Miss Scarlet.
等等
WILLIAM: Wait!
威廉
William.
走吧
Shall we?
晚上好 先生
Good evening, sir.
谢谢你 先生
SERVANT: Thank you, sir.
谢谢
Thank you.
你父亲在哪
Where's your father?
他发电报说他有事耽搁了
Oh, he sent a telegram saying he would be delayed
很遗憾恐怕不能出席了
and sadly could no longer attend.
他还发电报了 什么时候发的
He sent a telegram? When?
就在我们刚离开时 但他要求你
Shortly before we left- - but he requested
无论如何都要陪同我
that you accompany me nonetheless.
我以为那是他该做的事
I thought that's what he was doing.
-谢谢   -客气
Thank you. Of course.
到底是怎么回事
What exactly is going on?
好吧
Very well.
我带你来这是稍微找了点假借口
I may have brought you here under slight false pretenses.
我们租的房子是
Mr. Parker's mother owns the leasehold
帕克先生母亲的
to our property. Hm.
她非常希望我能和她儿子
She is very keen for myself and her son
加深一下了解
to become better acquainted
而我则 正相反
and I am...less keen.
他好像对你根本不感兴趣啊
He doesn't seem that interested in you.
感谢上帝的怜悯
Thank the Lord for small mercies.
你总喜欢这么撒谎吗
Do you always lie this much?
我没撒谎啊
It wasn't a lie.
只是暂时偏离了真相而已
It was a temporary departure from the truth.
好吧
： Okay.
但我向你保证 以后再也不会骗你了
But you have my word, I'll never lie to you again.
当然 你一向遵守承诺
And, of course, you always keep to your word.
一向
Always.
干杯
Slainte.
Cheers.
那么
So.
你到底跟我父亲在做什么事
What exactly are you doing with my father, anyway?
他说过你会问起 然后他让我不要告诉你
He said you'd ask that, and he said not to tell you.
行吧
Very well.
但也许有一天 我会见到你父亲
But perhaps one day, I shall meet your father
然后我也不把他说的事告诉你
and he and I will share a secret.
希望你能找到他
Good luck finding him.
你不是说这里有吃的吗
I thought you said there'd be real food.
应该有面包托吧
There should be canapes somewhere.
什么叫面包托
What are canopies?
是一种餐前小点 而且你读的不对
Oh, they are small snacks, and it's pronounced"can- ah- pay. "
豆子罐头吗
Can of peas?
不是
No, it
你是逗我呢吗
: Are you teasing me?
好吧 应该有服务生在附近
ELIZA: Well, there should be a waiter somewhere.
我看能不能叫他过来
I'll see if I can catch his eye.
伊莱沙
Eliza.
耐心点嘛
ELIZA: Just be patient.
我目睹了一起谋杀
: I witnessed a murder.
我和你父亲就是在做这事
That's what I'm doing with your father.
他想让我帮他抓住凶手
He wants my help trying to find the killer.
而我刚刚找到他了
And I think I've found him.
干杯
Cheers.
MAN: Cheers!
-你确定是他吗  -非常确定
Are you sure it was him? As sure as I can be.
-你知道他叫什么吗  -不知道
Do you know his name? No.
-我回去问他  -你说什么
I shall go back in and ask him. And say what?
我朋友认为你是个杀人犯 你叫什么名字
"My friend thinks you're a murderer- - what's your name? "
-我肯定会用更优雅的方式来表达  -不行
Well, I imagine I'll find a more elegant way to put it. No.
我们去找你父亲把他带到这来
Let's go and find your father and bring him here.
如果我们能告诉他嫌犯的名字
It would help his inquiries if we could at least
一定会对他的讯问有帮助的
tell him the name of our suspect.
我们的嫌犯 这事跟你一点关系都没有
Our suspect? This has nothing to do with you.
-快点 我们走了  -好吧
Come on, we're leaving. Very well.
我去找鲁伯特
I'll go find Rupert.
他的司机肯定能送我们到地方
I'm sure his driver will take us wherever we need to go.
我们外面见
I'll meet you outside.
好吧
Fine.
一只野鸡也没见到
Not a single bloody pheasant to be seen.
真不知道他为什么组织大家12月份打猎
Now, why on Earth he held a shoot in December,
那家伙就是个傻瓜
I'll never know- - the man's a bloody fool.
能看出来你继承了你母亲的魅力
Well, I can see you have your mother's charm.
我今天早些时候遇到了她 真是位吸引人的女士
I met her earlier today- - an inspiring lady.
你不是穿过半个大厅
Now, you didn't walk halfway across this room
只为了跟我谈论我母亲吧
to talk to me about my mother.
我说过了 我们之前好像在哪见过
Well, as I said, I believe we have met before.
也许
Well, perhaps
你那么说只是想
you were just saying that to...
引起我的注意
gain my attention.
请你把手拿开
Kindly remove your hand.
我会挪开
Oh, I would do.
如果你是真心的
If you meant it.
不知道你
I wonder if you're aware
清不清楚 一个人被猫被狗咬
that the worst bite a person can receive
都没有被人咬更可怕
is not from a rat or dog, but a fellow human being.
唾液中的细菌
There are bacteria in the saliva
会导致感染 血液中毒
that can cause infection, blood poisoning,
在某些情况下还会导致截肢
and, in some cases, amputation.
很高兴跟你交谈
A pleasure speaking to you.
托马斯·哈珀·琼斯 哈珀·琼斯夫人的儿子
Thomas Harper Jones, son of Lady Harper Jones
而且几乎是我见过的最惹人厌的男人
and quite the most obnoxious man I've ever met.
什么 你跟他交谈过了
What, you spoke to him?
我们需要知道要对付的是什么人
We needed to know what kind of man we were dealing with.
我们
We? l
我父亲目前
My father is under
压力非常大
an awful lot of strain at the moment.
如果这个人不是他要找的
It would be unfair to waste his time.
浪费他的时间就不太合适了
if this is not the man he seeks.
而且我认为
And it is my belief
在告诉他任何事之前
that you and I should investigate the matter further
我们俩应该再深入调查一下
before telling him anything.
同意吗
Agreed?
真是够了 丽兹 你在想什么啊
For God's sakes, Lizzie, what were you thinking?
是我的错 我想查出他的姓名
It was my fault- - I wanted to find out his name.
如果我知道她带威廉去了派对
IVY: If I had known she had taken William to the party,
我绝不会说别的 但是我
I would never have said anything, but I
我们晚点再聊这事
We'll get to that, believe me.
-你确定是他吗  -确定
Are you sure it was him? Certain.
你告诉其他人了吗
And you've told no one else of this?
只有伊莱沙
Just Eliza.
哈珀·琼斯一家在当地有钱有势
The Harper Jones family are rich and influential,
还有很多当权的朋友
with powerful friends.
这事暂时只能我们知道
It is vital this stays between us for now.
-我能建议  -不能
Might I suggest...No.
-你不知道我要说  -我知道
You don't know what I was going to...Yes, I do.
夜深了
It's late.
我们明天再谈吧
We will talk of this tomorrow.
你跟艾薇去吧 她会带你去你房间
Go with Ivy she'll show you to your room.
丽兹 你等会
Lizzie, wait.
-我不想再跟你吵了  -我也是
I'm tired of arguing. Yes, as am I.
我知道你想跟随我的脚步
Look, I know you wish to follow in my footsteps.
但是我之前就跟你说过
But, as I have told you before,
这不可能
it is impossible.
所以 我的余生就要与
So, instead, I'm to spend the rest of my days
那些最无知最愚钝的人们一起喝茶度过
drinking tea with the dullest people known to humanity.
生活已经很艰难了 丽兹
Life's hard enough already, Lizzie.
别再搅和到这种事里面来了
Don't get involved with this.
拜托
Please.
日安 帕克太太
Good day, Mrs. Parker!
早上好
Good morning.
早上好 帕克太太
Ooh, good morning, Mrs. Parker.
斯嘉丽小姐
Miss Scarlet.
谢谢你这么短时间内还能赶过来
Thank you for coming at such short notice.
不得不说收到你一起散步的邀请
I confess to being pleasantly surprised
我还是很惊喜的
to receive your invitation for a walk.
昨天你似乎对此还毫无兴趣
Yesterday, you seemed somewhat disinterested.
我只是太集中注意力了
I was merely concentrating, that was all.
毕竟我不想错过任何智慧珠玑
I didn't want to miss any pearls of wisdom.
鲁伯特告诉我你们昨晚过的很开心
Rupert tells me you had a most pleasant evening.
所以估计他肯定会再来拜访你
I would not be surprised if he calls on you again.
我也希望如此呢
I certainly hope so.
昨晚确实特别美好
It was a splendid evening, indeed.
说到昨晚
Speaking of which,
我想提个大胆的建议 不知道合不合适
I wondered if I might be so bold as to make a suggestion.
很抱歉错过了昨晚的盛宴
MRS. PARKER: Iam sorry to have missed the festivities last night.
你也知道我之前就有安排了
As you know, I had a prior engagement
但是斯嘉丽小姐昨晚过的非常愉快
But Miss Scarlet had the most marvelous time
并坚持来亲自表达谢意
and insisted on coming to thank you in person.
真是太有心了
How very kind.
我唯一的遗憾就是我们俩没时间交谈
My only regret is that you and I did not find time to talk.
我很乐意听您多聊聊自己和您的家人
I'd love to hear more about you and your delightful family.
您女儿 当然 还有您儿子
Your daughter, of course, and, indeed, your son.
应该是叫托马斯吧
Thomas, I believe?
乐意之至
It would be my pleasure.
-请跟我来吧  -谢谢
Do please follow me. MRS. PARKER: Thank you.
这姑娘真是讨人喜欢呢
LADY HARPER JONES: What a charming young lady.
是不是
MRS. PARKER: Isn't she?
是他吗
HENRY: Is that him?
就是他
That's him.
好 我觉得你最好等在这
Right, I think it best you wait here.
他昨晚在派对上可能见过你了
He might have seen you at the party.
你打算怎么做
What are you going to do?
见机行事
Tread carefully.
小偷吗 这可新鲜了
THOMAS: Pickpockets? That's news to me.
我没听说啊
I've heard nothing of it.
在这条街上
I'm afraid there's been a spate
就发生了一连串这样的事 先生
of such incidents in this very street, sir.
上次发生在两天前吧
The last incident was, uh, two days ago.
好像是傍晚6点左右
Early evening, about 6: 00.
那时你在这附近吗
Were you, uh, were you here at that time?
不在
No.
那你在哪
Where were you?
这有什么重要的吗
Why does that matter?
有时候小偷就喜欢把你这种绅士
Well, sometimes pickpockets target a gentleman
当做目标 然后跟踪他们 去同样的地方
such as yourself, and follow him from wherever he's been.
饭店 酒店
A restaurant, hotel.
如果我们能找出他们的规律
If we can establish a pattern,
也许能帮我们抓到他们
it might help us catch them.
我在另一个俱乐部里
I was at my other club.
奥斯曼帝国 格雷旅馆路上
The Ottoman, on Gray's Inn Road.
我一整晚都在那
I was there all night
到达和离开的时候都没看见任何可疑的人
and saw nothing untoward upon my arrival or my exit.
很高兴听你这么说
Very glad to hear it.
最近的调查
: The, um, the investigation
又出现了令人不安的转折
has taken a rather sinister turn of late.
我们认为其中一个小偷
We believe one of the thieves
可能杀死了一个私家侦探
may have murdered a private detective.
私家侦探吗
A private detective? Mm.
亚瑟·沃利斯先生 一个好人
Mr. Arthur Wallis- good man.
之前做过警察
Former police officer.
你为什么只跟我一个人聊这事
Why is it just me you're talking to?
我打算跟这里的所有先生都聊聊
Oh, I intend to speak to all the gentlemen here.
只是碰巧先看到了你
I just happened to catch your eye first.
而且因为我丈夫在印度群岛
And, with my husband away in the Indies,
托马斯开始负责伦敦的事务
Thomas has been running our affairs in London.
那可真是重担在肩啊
That must be quite a burden to carry.
你有注意到他最近的行为有什么变化吗
Have you noticed any change in his behavior of late?
行为变化
Change in his behavior?
斯嘉丽小姐
Miss Scarlet,
你一直在不停的问有关托马斯的事
you have done nothing but ask questions about Thomas.
我可得提醒你一下
I would remind you
昨晚陪你的人是鲁伯特呢
it was Rupert who accompanied you last evening.
请原谅 我只是好奇而已
Forgive me, I was merely curious.
研究人性是我的一个小爱好
The study of human nature is something of a hobby of mine.
夫人
Hm. ANNIE: Madam,
您约的车到了
your appointment.
当然 谢谢你 安妮
Oh, of course- - thank you, Annie.
两位女士
Oh, ladies,
恐怕我要失陪了
I'm afraid you must excuse me.
我还有很多约会要参加
I have numerous appointments
因为目前没有车夫
that I must attend to, and as I am currently without a driver,
所以我只能租用马车了
I'm having to rely on hackney carriages,
而租车可真是太慢了
and I find that they take an age.
一个好车夫就像是一个好律师
A good driver is like a good lawyer.
你必须想尽办法把他们留住
You must hold on to him at all costs.
佩蒂弗就是如此
Pettifer was exactly that.
他为我们工作很多年了
He'd been with us for years.
但是他和托马斯
But he and Thomas
拌了几句嘴 第二天一早他就离开了
had cross words, and he left the very next morning.
他们拌嘴了 因为什么啊
They had cross words? What about?
我们就不再占用您宝贵的时间了
We shall take up no more of your valuable time.
走吧 斯嘉丽小姐
Come, Miss Scarlet.
不好意思
Oh, forgive me.
我刚才喝了太多茶
I have taken rather too much tea
走之前要先去个地方
and there is a room I must visit before we leave.
安妮
Annie,
带斯嘉丽小姐去吧
show Miss Scarlet where she needs to go.
那个马车夫佩蒂弗
This carriage driver, Pettifer,
跟哈珀·琼斯先生吵架的那个
the one who argued with Mr. Harper Jones.
你认识他吗
Did you know him?
认识
Yes, ma'am.
我去哪能找到他
Where might I find him?
我为他们家人做车夫很多年了
I was their driver for years- - whole family.
约翰逊·哈珀·琼斯 托马斯的父亲 他是个好人
Jonathan Harper Jones, Thomas's father, he was a good man.
跟他儿子不一样
Unlike his son.
托马斯还是个孩子时我就认识他了
I've known Thomas since he was a boy.
一看就知道他不是个好人
You could tell he was a wrong un.
所有人都知道
Everyone knew it
据我所知
As I understand it,
你们俩因为一件事吵了起来
the two of you had cross words about something.
那是几周前的事了
Well, that was a few weeks back.
我
I was, um,
我带着马车在房子前面
I was bringing the horse and carriage round the front
准备送他去他要去的地方
of the house to take him wherever he was going.
然后我注意到萨姆森 就是那匹马
And I noticed that Samson- that's the horse- -
我发现他瘸了 然后托马斯
I noticed he was lame, then Thomas,
他匆匆出现 说他要迟到了
he come rushing out, saying he was late
马瘸了也没啥大事
and the horse'd be fine.
我说 不行 先生
I said, "No, sir.
那匹马需要治疗
That horse needs medical attention. "
可他不在乎 他出来时就有点醉醺醺的
Well, he didn't care, he was drunk already.
他把我推开 自己跳上了车夫的位子
He pushed me out the way, jumped in the driver's seat,
然后赶着车就走了 第二天一早
and rode off; the next morning,
我注意到马车已经回到了马厩
I noticed the carriage was back in the stables
可怜的老萨姆森还被拴在车旁
still attached to poor old Samson.
他的腿更严重了 一直在流血
His leg was worse- - it was bleeding badly.
至于马车 也弄得都变形了
And as for the carriage, well, it was all bent and buckled.
可怜的老萨姆森 他 他只能被人道毁灭了
Poor old Samson, he had, he had to be destroyed.
那时候起我就决定 再也不能为他工作了
That's when I knew I couldn't work for him no longer.
你觉得他驾着马车撞到什么东西了吗
You believe he hit something with the carriage?
或者是什么人
Or someone.
你说是几周前
You say this was a few weeks ago.
具体什么时候
When, exactly?
你到底在干什么啊
What on Earth are you doing?
别担心 我 我会收拾好的
Don't worry, I'lI, I'II clean it up.
那是必须的啊 女士
You most certainly will, young lady.
你到底在干嘛
What are you doing?
我在找父亲的旧报纸
I was looking for Father's old newspapers.
他通常会保存一个月的报纸
He usually keeps them for at least a month.
他说这些都是宝贵的参考资料
He says they are an invaluable source of reference.
而且你知道吗 很多罪行
And did you know, many crimes
在报警之前会先告诉给记者
are reported to journalists before the police?
你又知道吗 自己头发上
Do you know that you've a piece
粘了块发霉的面包
of moldy bread in your hair?
我整个家都翻过了
I've searched the house
可是完全找不到任何旧报纸
and couldn't find any old papers anywhere.
我在想是不是都被丢掉了
I wondered if perhaps they'd been thrown out.
我跟他说要留就放在警局
Well, I told him to keep them at work.
我受够了一堆破报纸堆在家里占地方了
I got fed up with them cluttering up the place.
我会让托马斯·哈珀·琼斯前来做讯问
I'lI ask Thomas Harper Jones to come in for an interview.
他可能已经采取措施来堆砌自己的不在场证明了
He's probably taken steps to shore up his alibi,
但谎言越多 漏洞也就越多
but the more lies there are, the more cracks can appear.
你觉得他和死去的沃利斯先生
What do you think the connection is
有什么关系呢
to the dead Mr. Wallis?
不确定 我需要你一份完整的供词
I'm not sure- I'll need a full statement from you,
把你看到的一切都说出来
outlining everything you saw.
什么鬼
What on Earth...?
她又做了什么啊
What has she done now?
怎么了
What is it?
来这跟我碰头 丽兹
"Meet me here. Lizzie. "
具体是哪
Where, exactly?
到了
DRIVER: Whoa! Here we go.
把我们叫到这来你最好有足够的理由
There'd better be a damn good reason for this.
当然有 我保证
There is, I assure you.
萨玛里斯先生和太太
Mr. and Mrs. Samaris
是从塞浦路斯来的
are originally from the island of Cyprus.
萨玛里斯先生不会说英文
Mr. Samaris doesn't speak any English,
但是他妻子英文很好
but his wife has been good enough
可以帮我们进行翻译
to translate our conversation.
几周前 萨玛里斯先生下班回家
A few weeks ago, Mr. Samaris was on his way back from work
结果在大街上被一辆马车撞倒
when he was hit by a horse and carriage in the street.
当时天色已晚 没有其他人 马车也没停
It was late, no one was around, and the carriage didn't stop.
警察找不到车夫
The police were unable to find the driver,
你们从我留在桌上的报纸
as you'll have read in the newspaper article
应该也看到了
I left on your desk.
他瘸了
MRS. SAMARIS: He is crippled.
所以我们才去找私家侦探
That is why we went to the detective.
亚瑟·沃利斯吗
Arthur Wallis?
没错
Hm. Exactly.
沃利斯先生人很好 没收他的初始费用
Mr. Wallis was kind enough to waive his initial fee.
而且说只有在罪犯被绳之以法的情况下
Payment would be made only
才会收他们的钱
if the culprit was brought to justice.
你丈夫看到了驾车的人吗
And did your husband see the man that was driving that carriage?
是的
MRS. SAMARIS: Yes.
他把外貌描述给警察了
He gave a description to the police,
但他们什么都没有做
but they didn't do anything.
他说 就是照片里的那个人
He says, "This is the man in the photograph. "
-这张照片  -对
This photograph. MR. SAMARIS: Yeah.
就是托马斯·哈珀·琼斯
Of Thomas Harper Jones.
而且我认为
And it is my belief
沃利斯先生找到了哈珀·琼斯 并且跟他当面对质了
that Mr. Wallis found Harper Jones and confronted him
同时威胁他要把这事告诉警察
with the threat of reporting him to the police.
而这
And that...
就是为什么哈珀·琼斯杀了他
...is why Harper Jones murdered him.
我聪明的女儿
My clever girl.
他要收我5基尼
THOMAS: Five guineas he tried to charge me.
于是我对他说
So I said to him,
你知道我的家族背景吗
"Do you have any idea who my family is? "
他就闭嘴了
Well, that shut him up.
托马斯·哈珀·琼斯
Thomas Harper Jones?
又干嘛
What is it now?
我还有几个问题要问你
I have a few more questions for you.
现在我不方便
Well, it's not a convenient time.
我不是在请求你
This is not a request.
你的证词写完了吗
Have you finished your witness statement?
正在检查拼写错误
Just checking for spelling mistakes.
真希望你写学校作业时也能这么投入
I wish you'd been this dedicated to your schoolwork.
我们搜查了哈珀·琼斯梅菲尔的住宅
So, we searched the Harper Jones Mayfair residence.
在那里发现了亚瑟·沃利斯
He had the Samaris case file
正在调查的萨玛里斯先生一案的档案
that Arthur Wallis was working on.
在里面 他称哈珀·琼斯为嫌疑人
In it, he names Harper Jones as a suspect, so,
再加上威廉姆的目击证词
that, combined with William's eyewitness account,
也许足够提起诉讼了
may be enough to secure a conviction.
也许吗
May be?
他肯定会出钱请最好的律师
He'll have the best lawyers money can buy.
没办法保证结果
Nothing's guaranteed.
那现在怎么办
So...What now?
我们会走指认嫌疑人流程
Well, we'll arrange a line- up of suspects.
-然后让威廉确认  -不是 我是说
I'lI ask William to formally...No, I mean,
我现在怎么办
what now for me?
这件事证明了我的能力吧
Surely this proves where my abilities lie.
我从未 一刻都没有怀疑过你的能力 丽兹
Never, not for one moment, did I doubt your ability, Lizzie.
你坚韧不拔
You are tenacious
足智多谋
and resourceful, and every bit
和这里的任何男人一样能干
as capable as any man here.
但你的想法不变
But your opinion remains unchanged.
我的想法并不重要
My opinion doesn't matter.
问题是整个世界的想法
It's the rest of the world that's the problem.
谁知道未来会发生什么变化呢
Who knows what will happen in the future?
但是就目前来看
But, for now
这不是我能走的路
This is not the path that I can follow.
非常抱歉
I'm so sorry.
早上好
Good morning.
威廉 早上好
William, good morning.
我听说你要回学院去了
I heard you were going back to college.
我就想过来跟你告个别
I thought I'd come and say goodbye.
他们答应给我第二次机会
They've agreed to give me a second chance.
其实已经是第三次了
Third, actually.
我想找几本书带上
I was just looking for some books to take,
结果却找到了这个
but I found this instead.
我不知道你养狗了呢
Hm, I didn't know you had a dog.
不在了 他死了
Not anymore- - he died.
你不介意我继续打包行李吧
Do you mind if I carry on packing?
我还要赶火车
I have a train to catch.
不介意 你继续
No, no, carry on.
我听说你找到地方住了
So, I hear you found somewhere to live.
嗯 是在斯特普尼的一个招待所
Hm, it's a lodging house in...Stepney?
你父亲帮我付了头个月的租金
Your father paid the first month's rent.
我 我说等我有钱就还他
I, I said I'd pay him back when I can.
希望不会太久
Shouldn't be too long, hopefully.
今天下午我就要去见
I've got a meeting with the recruiting sergeant
招募巡佐了
this afternoon.
招募巡佐
The recruiting sergeant?
对 我想加入警队
I'm thinking about joining the police.
你父亲帮我说了好话
Your father said he'd put in a word for me.
你要加入警队
You're joining the police?
我还不知道自己要不要加入
I still don't know if I actually will,
但他们说赚钱不少
but they say the money's quite good.
天知道我穿上制服会是什么样子
: God knows what I'll look like in the uniform.
这该死的箱子
Oh, this damn thing!
-我来帮你  -不用 我自己能搞定 谢谢
Here, let me. No, I'm more than capable of doing it myself, thank you.
我说什么让你不开心了吗
Have I upset you?
不是 只是这条 狗
No, it's just this...dog.
这 这愚蠢的该死的狗
Just this, this, this stupid, damn dog!
这不公平 威廉 不公平
It's not fair, William, it's not fair.
拜托了
Please, just
别哭
Stop crying.
丽兹 快下来了
IVY: Lizzie! Come on, young lady!
你会迟到的
You'll be late!
我得走了 斯嘉丽小姐
I must be going- Miss Scarlet.
你没事吧
Are you all right?
没事 我挺好的 谢谢
Yes- - quite well, thank you.
威廉
William?
: William!
我想喝一杯
: I need a drink.
我去给你拿水
I'll get you some water.
我想要杯双份威士忌
I was thinking more a double whisky.
我是去哪了 干了什么啊
Oh, what have I gone and done to myself now?
给
Here, shh.
你害我们担心死了 威廉
You've had us all so worried, William.
我天天都来看你
I've been coming every day to see you,
就坐在旁边陪你 希望你能醒过来
to sit with you, hoping you'd wake up.
现在你 现在你真醒过来了
: And now you, and now you have!
我的天 听着我这么 你感觉如何
Oh, my, listen to me going onhow are you feeling?
如果你 你能让我说句话
If you'd, if you'd just let me speak...
听到你的声音真高兴 威廉
It's good to hear your voice, William.
真的好高兴
It's good indeed!
我再给你倒点水吧
Can I get you some more water?
我想喝威士忌
I prefer whisky.
没有威士忌给你
You're not having whisky.
这样舒服点吗
Is this comfortable?
-不太舒服 尤其是你这样  -抱歉
Not particularly, when you do that. I'm sorry.
我今早一到
I arrived this morning to be greeted
就看到了一个大惊喜
by a most pleasant surprise.
你好啊 伊莱沙
Bonjour, Eliza.
我把生意交给你是指望你越搞越好
I leave you a business that is thriving
可回来一看马上都快支撑不下去了
and come back to find it barely surviving!
我不着急回去呢
I'm in no rush to go back
那份工作对你来说就是一切啊
That job is everything to you.
并非是一切吧
Not everything